QuranCode1433 Lite Edition

► Ctrl+Click a word to display verses with related words from the same root.
► Calculate and display the values of selected text/selection/Book in any numerology system.
► Updated root database by Ali Adams and Yudi Rohmad (Indonesia).
► Display number of verses before and after current verse within its chapter and within the whole Quran.
► Calculate the LetterFrequencySum for any user phrase in each verse in all selected chapters.
► Waw as a word option in any Simplified text mode.
► Shadda as a double letter option in any Simplified text mode.
► BismAllah chapter prefixes option in any Simplified text mode. BismAllah of surat Al-Fatiha is not a prefix but verse #1.
► Multi-select in Letter Frequency List with immediate sum prime factorization.
► Find sentences by numbers (words/letters/value).
► Display Original text but use Simplified29 word/letter counts.
► Display chapter detailed info as you move over each chapter.
► FindByNumbers words / sentences / verses / chapters by numbers, words, letters, unique letters, value, or their sums.
► FindByNumbers word ranges / verse ranges / chapter ranges by sum of numbers, chapters, verses, words, letters, unique letters, value, or their sums.
► FindByNumbers supports all comparison operators and MultipleOf N and IndivisibleBy N (with user-defined remainder).
► Play Previous verse and Play Next verse buttons added to mp3 player.
► Search in current text mode or in all text modes in case user enters non-simplified letters in a simplified text mode.
► Search by root with multi-root support and +/- include/exclude options.
► WORDS search supports "-" and "+" at word start to exclude or include words respectively.
► Silence between verses from 0.0 to 2.0 times the verse length in 0.1 increments.
► Direct chapter/verse entry (1, 3-4, 5:55, 3-4:19, 6:19-23, 24:35-27:62).
► Direct page, station, part, group, half, quarter, bowing, verse, word, letter entry (1, 1-2, ...).
► Word grammar in Arabic and English adapted from http://corpus.quran.com
► Word meaning and transliteration as mouse moves over words.
► Auto-download recitations in any reciter from http://everyayah.com with auto-repeat 2, 3, 5, 7 or unlimited times.

God bless and protect those who follow His Commandments.

Ali Adams
qurancode.com
God >
